luxuryherveleger.com 2011-07-20

# Privacy&Policy-Herve Leger Clothing,Herve Leger Sale UK Store,Up 50% Off

## Privacy&Policy

 **Privacy Notice**

[www.luxuryherveleger.com](http://www.luxuryherveleger.com/) respectsyour privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide youwith the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, werecord a variety of information from your visit to our site. To better protectyour privacy, we provide the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information iscollected and used. 

**How does** **[www.luxuryherveleger.com](http://www.luxuryherveleger.com/)** **use my personal information?** **** **Internal Use:** We use your personal information to process your orderand provide you with customer service. We may use your personal informationinternally to collect general information about visitors to this Site, improveSite content and layout, improve our outreach, and market our services andproducts. **Communication with You:** We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our Site and your orders. Allcustomers must provide an email address to allow communication with [www.luxuryherveleger.com](http://www.luxuryherveleger.com/) regarding orders placed. We may send you a confirmation email after youregister with us as well as service-related announcements as necessary (forexample, temporary suspension of service for maintenance.) You may also submityour email address to request notification when we receive a new brand, productstyle or product, or to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers.You can unsubscribe or opt out of future emails at any time (see the OptOut/Corrections section below for more details).

 **Does[www.luxuryherveleger.com](http://www.luxuryherveleger.com/) evergive out my personal information?**

We sell merchandise, not information — We do not sell, rent, trade,license, or otherwise disclose your personal or financial information toanyone, except in the following specific situations:

 **Third-party service providers** : Like most catalog and Internetwholesalers, we sometimes use third-party service providers to perform specificfunctions on our behalf. Any information disclosed to them is solely to help intheir provision of service. For example, we provide your name, shippingaddress, email and phone number to partners such as DHL and UPS in order toguarantee delivery of your orders, and we may use relevant customer informationin order to monitor the quality of the third party’s service.

Similarly, we must provide your credit card number to financial servicesorganizations such as credit card processors and issuers in order to processpayments. We protect all submissions of your credit card number forauthorization with state-of-the-art data encryption. (More on this below in theData Security section.)

 **Legalrequirement to disclose information:** We may be required to disclose information ifsubpoenaed, served with a court order or requested by law-enforcement officialsconducting investigations, or if we are otherwise required by law to disclosesuch information. We will also release personal information when necessary toprotect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. Forexample, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud, or to preventfraud by users who attempt fraud or other illegal activity on our Site.  
 **  
 **Merger and/or sale of assets:**** We do not normally sell, trade or rent personal information   
to other companies in the course of our business. However, it is possible thatwe might acquire, merge with or be acquired by another company, or that wemight dispose of some or all of our assets, in which case your personalinformation could be disclosed to another company, subject to the PrivacyNotice in effect.  
 **  
 **Non-personally identifiableinformation:**** We may share information that does notidentify you or any user, such as the number of daily visitors to a particularpage, or the size of an order placed on a certain date, with third parties suchas advertising partners.

 **DATA SECURITY**

This Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative proceduresto safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. We use SecureSockets Layer ("SSL") encryption to safeguard all financialtransactions done through this Site. We also protect your personal informationinternally by granting only employees who are providing a specific serviceaccess to your personal information. Finally, we only work with third-partyservice providers who we believe adequately secure all computer hardware. For example, visitors to our Site access servers kept in a secure physicalenvironment and behind an electronic firewall.
